A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Business Interests, Series C FA312
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Banks
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Amerex Holding Corporation, 1934-1937 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    Defunct Chase Corporation (subsidiary of Bank) still held various stocks, especially American Express Company. Corporation changed name to Amerex, distributed shares to Bank stockholders. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. sold his stock.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Account #2, 1931-1935 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    Opening of checking account for paying bills for the estates.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Account #4, 1932-1935 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    Account at Park Avenue branch; deposits for Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's use.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Rockefeller Center Branch, 1933-1960 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    Vault space Center branch for family, Rockefeller Boards, various companies. Transferring of accounts to new branch; attempts to build up Branch's deposits, aided by Nelson A. Rockefeller.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Stock Purchased for Group Account, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    Purchase of Chase stock by group formed for that purpose; relation with Metpotan Securities Corporation and Chase Securities Corporation.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Deposits for John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Personal Account, 1930-1939 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Loan for Mrs. Bosworth and E. C. Marsh, 1927-1936 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Member of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s church got Dr. Fosdick to ask John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to loan her $6,000. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. guaranteed Equitable Trust loan. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. paid most of the loan, 1931.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Chase Harris Forbes Corporation, 1917-1939 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    John D. Rockefeller subscribed to newly formed Chase Securities Corporation; Bertram Cutler became member of Executive Committee in this and in Chase Harris Forbes Corporation which purchased and distributed securities for Chase Securities Corporation. Divorcement of Chase Securities Corporation from Bank, liquidation of Chase Securities Corporation, complaints of employees. Material re First Boston Corporation and family's subscription to it.
  - Banks - Chase National Bank - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1946-1954 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller became member of Executive Committee; letters of congratulations.
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Suit Against Bank, 1933-1938 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    89C1A
  - Banks - Chase Bank - Suit Against Mr. Wiggins, 1933-1938 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    Attempt by stockholders to regain some of the high salary, bonuses and profits paid to Wiggins; heard by referee, settled out of court. Chase received $2,500,000. Complaints by stockholders against Wiggins. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, A. Wiggins.
  - Banks - Cleveland Banks and Trust Company, 1910-1927 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    Bertram Cutler analysis of Cleveland banks in which Foundation had stock in 1915; John D. Rockefeller deposits in some banks; requests for deposits. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler.
    89C2
  - Banks - Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company, 1933-1950 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    Description of philanthropic services; attempts to obtain business. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    89C3
  - Banks - Chemical Bank and Trust Company, 1940-1947 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    Tenants in Rockefeller Center; request for deposits declined. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise.
    89C4
  - Banks - County Trust Company, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. inactive account in bank; Rockefellers declined to buy interest in company. Background information on merger. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, Joseph Hughes.
    89C8
  - Banks - Equitable Trust Company, 1908-1931 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    At Frederick T. Gates' urging, John D. Rockefeller bought stock, 1911; placed Rockefeller representatives on Board. 1919, John D. Rockefeller largest stockholder, held one-sixth of total. Stock transferred to John D. Rockefeller, Jr., and General Education Board. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, H. E. Cooper, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    89E1
  - Banks - First National Bank of North Tarrytown, 1930-1946 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    $10,000 payroll account for Pocantico Hills estate kept at bank. Correspondents include Phillip Keebler.
    89F
  - Banks - Guaranty Trust Company, 1912-1938 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    Offer of stock declined; reports on bank. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Bertram Cutler.
    89G2
  - Banks - National City Bank, 1900-1951 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    John D. Rockefeller stock purchases, 1900, 1902; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. became a director, 1901; resigned in 1902. Dealings in stock; syndicate participation; checking account; bank tenant in Rockefeller Center. Stock holdings always small. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., J. Stillman, Henry Cooper, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    89N1
  - Banks - New York Trust Company, 1937-1952 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    Reports on the company.
    89N2
  - Banks - Tarrytown National Bank, 1904-1951 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. had small accounts; Robert Patterson, of the bank, friend of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler, Robert Patterson.
    89T1
  - Banks - Title Guarantee and Trust Company, 1902-1949 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    John D. Rockefeller had deposit, also owned some stock. Depression problems. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, E. L. Marston, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler.
    89T2
- Chase Safe Deposit Company
  - Chase Safe Deposit Company, 1933-1952 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    Rental of space for safe-keeping of family securities. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Robert W. Gumbel, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    103.4
  - Chase Safe Deposit Company - Access to Children's Vaults, 1933-1952 (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Bright Matter
  - Bright Matter - Pan American Railway Company, 1925-1931 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    John D. Rockefeller investment in South American railroad scheme; Uruguay government bought out company. Negotiations to settle bond accounts of previous investors; legal contest. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Bertram Cutler.
    54
  - Bright Matter - Pan American Railway Company, 1912-1925 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Bright Matter, 1923-1940 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    Attacks, civil suits against John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. by Charles Bright, an engineer, re South American railroad project. Rockefellers convinced Bright was mentally unbalanced. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Bright Matter - Col. Woody, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Bright Matter - "Vigilante", ca. November, 1932 (Box 140, Folder 1034)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Box 10, Folder 87.
  - Bright Matter - "Vigilante", September 1931 (Box 140, Folder 1035)
  - Bright Matter - "The Vigilant American", August 1929 (Box 140, Folder 1036)
  - Bright Matter - "Vigilante", June 1924 (Box 140, Folder 1039)
- China Industries Inc.
  - China Industries, Inc. - Stock Description, 1945-1954 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    Investment by Rockefeller Brothers Company in organization to trade and invest in China. Investment liquidated by 1950. Correspondents include Barton P. Turnbull, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    251
  - China Industries, Inc. - Stock Description - Certificate of Incorporation, etc., 1945-1954 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- Collins Brown Press
  - Collins Brown Press, 1920-1943 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions towards costs of publication of manual and other publications on old New York. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, H. C. Brown, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    26
  - Collins Brown Press - Contributions, 1922-1929 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- Colorado Fuel & Iron Company
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Miscellaneous, 1903-1917 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    J. C. Osgood's report on financial requirements; agreement between Colorado Fuel & Iron Company, John D. Rockefeller and Jay Gould to indemnify Gould and John D. Rockefeller as guarantors of Hearne's contract. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s denial that labor leaders were carrying on negotiations leading to union recognition in Colorado Fuel & Iron; E. S. Cowdrick's article on industrial relations. Map showing John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s inspection trip route. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, J. C. Osgood, E. V. Cary, G. P. Butler, E. Parmalee Prentice, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, J. F. Welborn.
    150
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Newspaper Articles, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s visit to Colorado; dedication of Ludlow monument. Industrial representation plan; labor troubles. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, W. MacKenzie King, Ivy Lee, E. H. Weitzel.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Newspaper Articles, 1914-1923 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Newspaper Articles, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Incorporation, By-Laws, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 0096A)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Colorado Industrial Plan Acknowledgements, 1916-1918 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    Letters of thanks from recipients of booklets; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s response. Correspondents include E. S. Cowdrick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, Starr J. Murphy, Charles O. Heydt, Ivy Lee, W. H. Taft, E. Marston, F. Green.
    150.2
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Colorado Industrial Plan Acknowledgements, 1916-1918 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Colorado Industrial Plan Acknowledgements - Acknowledgements from Editors, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    150.21
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Acknowledgements of Editorials re Plan, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. letters of thanks for editorials re Plan.
    150.23
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    150.25
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan - Appreciations - Atlantic Monthly, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan - Letters of Appreciation, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan - Appreciations - Hospital Sociological Data, 1916-1923 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan, 1916-1923 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    Operation of industrial relations plan by Midvale Steel and Cambria Steel Company. Miner's letter to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. re betterment of labor conditions; letters re plan in other companies. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Ivy Lee, Charles O. Heydt, Jerome Davis, W. MacKenzie King.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan - Appreciations - Study of Colorado Fuel and Iron Plan - Flaming and Hedges, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Letters Re Working of Plan - Appreciations - Correspondence with Companies re Forming Plans, 1919-1922 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    Inauguration and operation of plan by General Electric, Bethlehem Shipbuilding Corporation and other plants. List of firms adopting plans.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - General Correspondence, 1914-1924 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    Production costs; Weitzel's comments on industrial representation plan; Agnes Campbell's pamphlet "Constitutionalism in Industry." American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) complaint re censorship of Walsenberg Independent. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s comments on Matteson article, "Cooperation and Friendship in Industry." Dividends; minutes of Minnequa Steel Works Special Joint Conference; Park's protest of his dismissal. Stock sales; requests for advice and employment. Possibility of selling Fuel Company bonds. Correspondents include Cass Herrington, E. H. Weitzel, J. F. Welborn, Charles O. Heydt, Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., J. Gilchrist, LaMont Bowers, Thomas M. Debevoise, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, J. C. Hamilton.
    150.1
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - General Correspondence, 1924-1937 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - General Correspondence, 1938-1962 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - J. D. Gilchrist, 1914-1916 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    Attempts to be re-employed by Colorado Fuel & Iron; criticism of Company practice.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - By-Production, 1914-1916 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    Clarke's report on desirability of by-product coke production; McClement suggestion that tin plate mill be erected at Pueblo.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Coverdale and Colpitts Report, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    Report on value of Colorado Fuel & Iron capital stock, 1930. Cost of survey.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - A. J. Diamond Correspondence, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    Diamond's plea to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to meet with employees' representatives; closing of steel works Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA). Minutes of special joint conference.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - W. J. Dalton, 1915-1921 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    Claimed to be former employee, injured but receiving no compensation.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Dr. Corwin, 1915-1919 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. enthusiasm for Dr. Corwin's work and hospital; Corwin's trip to France to study use of antiseptics. Letters of appreciation from patients.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - E. S. Cowdrick, 1915-1924 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    Preparation of articles on industrial representation plan; report of tour of inspection. Efforts to locate other employment after dropped from Colorado Fuel & Iron during retrenchment program.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Re Weitzel's Pension, 1928-1942 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    Retirement arrangements; Weitzel's complaint of unfair treatment, appeals to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for help. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. tried to help, unable to do so.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - B. F. Matteson, 1928-1942 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    Retirement; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. $5,000 personal gift. Pension reduction; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. help.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Loan, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. loaned Welborn $20,000 for bank debts; further financial difficulties and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. help.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn, J. F. - General, 1923-1934 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Industrial Question, 1928-1940 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    Modifications in representation plan; 1933 unionization attempt. 1940, National Labor Relations Board banned plan on appeal by Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO); continued company plan at Steelworks. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur Woods, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur Roeder, J. F. Welborn.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Industrial Question, 1941-1950 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Roeder Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    Minutes of meeting of employees' representatives. Award of Certificate of Honor by Safety Association; list of directors and officers of subsidiary companies; survey of effect of repeal in time lost. Management problems. Roeder's resignation. Correspondents include Arthur Roeder, Thomas M. Debevoise, Bertram Cutler, Robert W. Gumbel, B. P. Turnbull.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Roeder Correspondence, 1937-1945 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Roeder Correspondence - Wage Reduction, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    Reduction of wages; requests that John D. Rockefeller, Jr. intervene; crank letters.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    Welborn's report on 1919 strike, business conditions. Denver ministers' tour of coal district. Newspaper comments re anti-union discrimination, explosion at mine. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledge of cooperation with Governor Sweet to avoid strike. Estimates of probable life of mines and quarries. Kenneth Chorley reports on trip to Colorado, Colorado labor situation. Reports on prices, shipments, orders, production. Personal gifts to Welborn by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Charles O. Heydt, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert W. Gumbel, Kenneth Chorley, Arthur Woods, Thomas M. Debevoise, J. Welborn, Ivy Lee, Alva Adams, E. H. Weitzel.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence, 1919-1922 (Box 15, Folder 0127A)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Improvements - Steel Mill, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. comments on recommendations for improvements at Steel Plant; cost.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Pueblo Flood, 1921-1924 (Box 15, Folder 0128A)
    Alva Adams efforts to get federal aid to prevent flood; Welborn's reports on damage. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledge to help rebuild destroyed homes, cancelled.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Leases to Oil Companies, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    Leases of ground for oil exploration work.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Natural Gas, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    Extension of natural gas into Denver; report on value of natural gas over producer gas at Minnequa; adoption of natural gas by Colorado Fuel & Iron.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Charles Kaiser, 1936-1944 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    Attempts to find employment for old mine superintendent; aid in sickness.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Bonus, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    Executive bonus plan; Welborn's comments on it.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welborn Correspondence - Gifts, 1930-1934 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s special gifts to Welborn.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Russell Sage Foundation, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    Ben Selekman's report on investigation of industrial relations plan; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s view that report was prejudiced against play; MacKenzie King's comments. Mary Van Kleeck's trip to Colorado; preparation of second report. Correspondents include J. F. Welborn, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Ivy Lee, Robert W. Gumbel, M. Van Kleeck, MacKenzie King.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Russell Sage Foundation, 1922-1925 (Box 16, Folder 0134A)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Russell Sage Foundation - Mr. R. W. DeForest, 1921-1924 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    Robert DeForest's assurances that report would not be published without prior conferences; Welborn's view that no one had talked to Selekman about Colorado situation.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - United Mine Workers of America, 1915-1922 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    Elmer Sommers visit to Starr J. Murphy re recognition of union, his allegations that John D. Rockefeller, Jr. refused to see him or discuss matter; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s denial of charge. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, J. F. Welborn, Elmer Sommers.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1927 Strike (Box 16, Folder 137)
    Industrial Workers of the World (IWW) call for strike; strikers' demands; report on Industrial Commission. Progress reports; confidential report on Industrial Workers of the World (IWW) activities.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1927 Strike, 1928-1931 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1927 Strike - Industrial Workers of the World (IWW) Newspaper Clippings, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1927 Strike - Memos re Strikes, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    Memos re 1913, 1919, 1921, 1927 strikes.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Stock Sold to Officials, 1918-1921 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    Purchase of stock by management; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s approval; list of purchasers; repurchases of stock by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1919 Steel Strike, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    Welborn's report on "Strikes in Coal and Steel Operations"; report of State Industrial Commission. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., MacKenzie King, J. F. Welborn, E. S. Cowdrick.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - 1919 Steel Strike - Corresopndence and Telegrams, 1919-1920 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    Conferences with employees' representatives; strike plans; reports on disorders, mediation progress. Employee thanks for encouragement and protection.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Minnequa hospital (Corwin Hospital), 1922-1935 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    Proposed survey of hospital; Corwin memo re hospital's needs. Death of Dr. Corwin; hospital name changed to Corwin Hospital. Correspondents include Kenneth Chorley, Thomas M. Debevoise, Dr. R. W. Corwin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., G. Vincent, J. Welborn, E. Lewinski-Corwin.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Elections, Resignations of Directors, 1903-1945 (Box 17, Folder 145)
    Elections of Greene, Starr J. Murphy, Ivy Lee, Bertram Cutler, Arthur Woods, Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Boulware as directors; resignation of Cooper, Greene, Bertram Cutler, Starr J. Murphy. 1920, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. retired. Election of Colorado men to Board. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, J. A. Writer, LaMont Bowers, J. F. Welborn, Thomas M. Debevoise.
    150.3B
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Financial Interests, 1914-1927 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    Statement of investments showing amount and book cost at end of each year. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Charles O. Heydt, Bertram Cutler.
    150.5
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Nurse, 1916-1917 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. agreement to pay nurse's salary; hiring of Clare V. Espe.
    150.7
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work, 1915-1922 (Box 17, Folder 0147A)
    Plans for Sunrise and Primero temporary hospitals; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. ideas re buildings. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. J. Hicks, L. W. Etsinger, E. S. Cowdrick.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Mr. C. Hicks - Personal, 1915-1917 (Box 17, Folder 148)
    Hicks spent August, 1915, in Colorado studying Colorado Fuel & Iron welfare work, appointed executive assistant to President; later assisted Standard Oil of New Jersey.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Bandstands, Uniforms for Band, 1916-1922 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    Specifications for bandstand and dancing pavillion at Cameron; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. agreed to build bandstand at several towns; purchase of uniforms.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Club Houses, 1915-1922 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    Plans for clubhouse; construction; memo re operation.
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Dispensary Building, 1915-1917 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company - Welfare Work - Churches, 1921-1925 (Box 17, Folder 152)